你们好  今日的特餐是蛤蜊浓汤
Hi. Today's special is clam chowder,
而今日的建议是别吃
and today's advice is don't eat it.
你们这里有蛋"卷福"吗
Do you have Eggs Benedict Cumberbatch?
本尼迪克特·康伯巴奇  在英剧《神探夏洛克》中
饰演的福尔摩斯有着卷发  所以又被粉丝叫"卷福"
玛丽  你今晚真是笑"杀"四方啊
You are really killing it tonight, Mary,
而且没留下任何证据
and leaving no evidence.
我们刚参加完"神夏大会"
We're coming from Sherlock-con.
像是"动漫大会"的《神探夏洛克》版
It's like Comic-Con, but for Sherlock Holmes fans.
比"动漫大会"酷多了
So it's way cooler.
原谅我失陪一下
Excuse me for a sec.
店里有另一位服务员
There's another waitress here
一定会很乐意看到你们的一举一动
who is gonna be a big fan of all of this.
带你看样东西  不用谢我了
You're welcome for what I'm about to show you.
你猜她们是什么来路
Look, guess what they are.
穿越时空的拉拉吗
Time-traveling lesbians.
-我们不是拉拉  -我是
- We're not lesbians. - I am.
她们是哪个活动结束后放出来的吗
What is this? What just let out?
低档商场大拍卖吗
A sale at the Burlington Coat Factory?
她们是《神探夏洛克》的死忠粉
They're Sherlock Holmes super-fans
刚参加完"神夏大会"
coming from a convention,
现在肯定有无数猫在家中独守空闺啊
which means there are a lot of cats home alone right now.
现在唯一的谜题是
Well, I'd say the only mystery
谁"阴门最鲜为君开"吧
is who here gets laid the least.
你们好啊
Hello.
华生  咱们突破盲点了
Cracked it, Watson.
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
打工
姐妹花
第十八集
第三季
打工
姐妹花
第十八集
第三季
翻校  明侦探赛腾新一
翻校  哈欠女灰原猫猫
后期
怪盗少女基德灰
时间轴 总监  哈欠女灰原猫猫
有个神夏粉
One of those Sherlock ladies
把她的腕隧道症护腕忘在这里了
left her carpal tunnel brace in here.
里面没有主人地址  不过有一张写着
No address, but there's a card that says,
"如发生紧急事故  请拨打1800-巧克力"
"In case of emergency, dial 1-800-chocolate."
许多公司喜欢选能与产品有关联的号码
chocolate对照电话键盘上的字母即是电话号
这我收下了
And I'll take that.
好了各位  又到了这重大时刻
Okay, everybody. It's that time again--
餐厅的春季大扫除
The diner's big spring clean!
天啊  六年一度又到来了吗
Oh, my God, has it been six years already?
可惜我刚得了腕隧道症
Too bad I just developed carpal tunnel.
好发于得做重复性腕部活动的职业
能造成手部麻木  无力  疼痛等症状
麦克斯演得出假中风吗
Max, do you think you can fake a stroke?
假中风  假高潮
Fake a stroke, fake an orgasm,
只要能偷懒  我啥都假得出
basically anything that will get me out of work.
我们有很多的活要干
Okay, we have lots of chores to do,
而且有人还得做二人份
and somebody will have to double up,
因为厄尔叫我今晚
because Earl asked me not to speak to him
不许再跟他说话
for the rest of the night.
大爷不是让你连我名字都不许提吗
Didn't I tell you to keep my name out your mouth?
姑娘们  我们把干活弄得好玩点如何
So, girls, what do you say we make it fun, huh?
我念出一项工作  想做的人就举手
I'll read a chore. You raise your hand.
清理灶台周围的油脂脏污
Scrape the fat puddle from under the stove!
没人要去吗
No takers?
下一项
Next.
清除冷藏库里的蜘蛛团伙
Clear the spider community in the walk-in!
没人要去吗
No takers?
下一项
Next.
清除洗碗盘区的蜘蛛团伙
Clear the spider community in the dish room!
也没人要去吗
No takers?
阿憨  抱歉  我不能清理  我得了腕隧道症
Han, sorry, I can't clean. I have carpal tunnel.
医生说我的手不能出力
The doctor says I can't put any pressure on my wrist.
阿憨  我也不能打扫  我下颚有病
And I can't clean either, Han. It's my jaw.
我得了"T.M.Z"病[其实是杂志名字]
I've got real bad "T.M.Z."
你们俩妞真是信口雌[屎]黄
Oh, you girls are so full of crap,
跟满是屎的男厕三号间一样
Like that third stall in the men's room.
有人要去吗
Any takers?
她当初面试的时候明明还很友善呢
She was so friendly in the job interview.
你好  麦克斯
Bonjour, Max.
尼可拉斯大厨
Oh, Chef Nicolas.
为什么我会在不是学校的地方见到你呢
Why am I seeing you outside of pastry school?
是因为我的果馅饼作业吗
Is it about my flan?
反正也没人爱吃那玩意嘛
Because no one likes that stuff anyway.
我不是为了那个而来的
Oh, no, that's not why I'm here.
我是想来跟卡洛琳谈谈
I want to speak to Caroline.
不过我的确给了你的果馅饼"C-"的分数
But, yes, I gave your flan a "C"-minus.
太平淡了
It was flat.
行  我去叫她
I'll go get her. Wow.
第一次有老师说我"平"呢
First time a teacher's ever called me flat.
我的手腕啊
Ow, ow, ow! Oh, my wrist!
我还以为是阿憨来了呢
Oh, I thought you were Han.
拜托  我比他还爷们两倍
Please, I'm twice the man he is.
尼可拉斯来了
Nicolas is here.
什么  不  不行
What? No, no, no!
他不可以闯入我私人生活
He can't be in my personal life!
在学校躲他
I'm having a hard enough time
就已经费了我很大劲了
avoiding working with him at pastry school.
我刚才把餐厅称为我的私人生活吗
Did I just call the diner my personal life?
好像吧  我没在听
I think so. I wasn't listening.
那我该怎么跟他说
So what do I tell him?
说我不跟他这种有妇之夫约会的
Tell him he's married, and I don't go out with married men.
跟他说我们之前只是调戏挑逗罢了
Tell him what we had was a passing flirtation.
一切到此为止  别纠缠了
Tell him now it's over, and he has to move on.
懂了  你死于厨房油脂走火
Got it, you died in a grease fire.
她还没到
She's not here yet.
那她会来吗
Oh, well, will she be coming?
她会来吗  短时间内是不会了
Will she be coming? Nope, not anytime soon.
好  那我发她短信  再见啦  麦克斯
Okay, I'll text her. Au revoir, Max.
先生  别误会我的意思
Sir, don't take this the wrong way,
但我想说你很帅
but you are one fine-looking man.
谢谢夸奖
Well, thank you very much.
你也是
And back at you.
能说点我不知道的吗
Tell me something I don't know.
你看  尼可拉斯给我发短信了
Look at this. Nicolas already texted me.
"愿意共进晚餐吗"  我该怎么办
"Will you have dinner?" What should I do?
装没看见啊  就跟我对那桌
Just ignore it, like I'm doing with that table
正对我招手的人一样
that's flagging me down right now.
我要为这尼可拉斯的事划下句点
I'm putting a stop to this Nicolas thing.
"等你跟你老婆离婚了
"I'll have dinner with you
我就跟你共进晚餐"
When you leave your wife."
送出出
And se-end.
你以后再敢说次"送出出"
If you ever say "se-end" again,
我就会让你"滚粗粗"
we're not gonna be "fri-ends."
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我刚从圣丹斯的独立电影节回来
I just got back from Sundance.
看了10部马克·鲁法洛电影
I saw ten Mark Ruffalo movies,
马克·鲁法洛  美国知名演员
曾出演多部电影  如《复仇者联盟》《惊天魔盗团》
还看到女演员凯瑟琳·基纳当DJ呢
and I got to watch Catherine Keener DJ.
又或者是别人吧
Well, whoever that is.
我也曾经出演过独立电影
I was in an indie movie once.
一男的拍我在运动用品店里的
Well, a guy filmed me eating a sloppy joe
更衣室里吃着邋遢乔三明治
in the dressing room of a Sport Chalet.
苏菲  你是怎么进圣丹斯电影节的呢
Sophie, how did you get into the Sundance film festival?
我跟一个大亨[大假发]约会了
Oh, I'm dating one of the bigwigs.
他是电影公司派对车的司机
He drives the Miramax party bus,
而且戴了顶大假发
and he wears a big wig.
所以我也在考虑自己拍一部片
So I'm thinking about producing my own movie.
你懂得  混进圈子嘛  宝贝
You know, getting into the biz, babe.
苏菲  如果你需要演员就告诉我
Sophie, if you need an actor, let me know.
但我只愿意正面全裸
But I'll only do full frontal.
正面局部全裸或"神雕"特写也行
I'll also do partial frontal or just penis close-ups.
如果你需要人来扮演天神  法官
And if you need someone to play God, a judge,
黑人影星摩根·费里曼曾在电影《冒牌天神》
《虚荣的篝火》《贝拉的魔法》中饰演过这些角色
或者当个坐在前院的老头
or an old guy sitting on a porch,
找我准没错
I'm your man.
大家继续给蛋糕裱花
Everyone, keep piping your cakes.
继续裱花
Keep piping.
麦克斯  快  快点  得多婊点花
Max, vite, vite. You need to pipe that more.
有意思  想当年我高中时的辅导员
That's funny, because my high school guidance counselor
总叫我少抽点大麻[裱花]
told me I need to pipe way less.
麦克斯  你今天进度落后了
Max, you are falling behind today.
你的迪克[鸡鸡]呢
Where's your Deke?
跟平日一样收在我裤裆里呢
In my pants, where it always is.
你是指迪克啊
Oh, you mean Deke.
到处都在传染流感  他也染上了
He's got the flu. It's everywhere.
这感冒甩都甩不掉  跟泰勒·斯威夫特一样
No one can shake it. It's like Taylor Swift.
也像咬人的斗牛犬
Yeah, or pitbull.
好了各位  下课时间到了
Okay, everyone, that's time.
下课  大家明天见
I will see you all tomorrow. Au revoir, class.
大厨再见
Au revoir, Chef.
走吧  走  走  走  走
Let's go. Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
走啦  快点  赶紧走人
Come on, come on, hurry. Let's get outta here.
干嘛这么着急
What's the hurry?
我妈发现我们偷住的房子
You sound like my mother whenever the real people
主人回家时就会像你这么催我
who lived in the house would come home.
我们现在得趁
We need to leave now,
尼可拉斯在他办公室里时开溜
while Nicolas is in his office.
我不想被他看到
I don't want him to see me.
我上一条短信就跟他把该说的说清楚了
I said everything I needed to say to him in my last text.
我闻到了奸情
Ooh, I smell scandal.
所以我在楼梯间里躲了一整天了
So I've been hiding in the stairwell all day.
你猜楼梯间通向哪里了
Guess where those stairs go.
一间有十个越南女人的房间
A room where ten Vietnamese women
她们正在山寨明年款的普拉达
are making next year's "Prada."
她们十分不喜欢"访客"哦
And they do not like visitors.
原来你跑去那里啦
Oh, is that where you were?
他之前也问过我  我就说你去拉屎了
'Cause he asked me, so I told him you were pooping.
麦克斯  你怎么能说我去拉屎了
Max, don't tell him I'm pooping!
这事又没什么好可耻的  卡洛琳
There's no shame in it, Caroline.
人生自古谁无屎
Everyone poops.
我就没
I don't.
我就吃  消化  然后会有天使
I just eat, digest, and then an angel comes
乘着夜色飞来将便便取走
and takes it away in the night.
抱歉  强哥  这是私人谈话
Excuse me, John. This is private.
是我们姑娘们之间的密语
It's just between us girls.
我知道啊  所以我才站在这边
I know. That's why I'm standing here.
好了  我也好了  等我拿上
Okay, I'm ready. Let me just grab
这个买给迪克的药吧
the medicine I got for Deke.
真有爱  你给他买抗生素了吗
Aw, that's sweet. You got him antibiotics?
不是  我买了维柯丁  我想他舒服点
No, I got him vicodin. I want him to feel better.
是一种鸦片类麻醉性镇痛药物
是处方药  有成瘾性  《豪斯医生》的爱用药
我只要走过走廊到达电梯的期间
I just have to make it down the hall
不要被尼可拉斯看见就行了
until the elevator without Nicolas catching me.
就像是成人版的青蛙过街游戏
Oh, like sexual frogger.
游戏结束  你的青蛙被车碾死了
Game over. Your frog just got hit by a car.
卡洛琳你在这里啊
Caroline, there you are.
我总觉得你可以在故意避开我
I can't help feeling you're avoiding me or something.
哪有避开你  我是去...
Avoiding you? No! I've been...
拉屎了
Pooping.
整整5小时吗
For five hours?
她的便便有点宅
She had a reluctant stool.
帮倒忙了吗
Oh, is that not helping?
卡洛琳  我有事想跟你说
Caroline, I have something to tell you.
能聊两句吗
Can we talk?
我们都在等呢
We're all waiting.
你还记得你那条短信中说
You know in your text how you said that
"只要我还是有妇之夫  你就不跟我共进晚餐"
you won't have dinner with me while I'm still married?
我的电视硬盘录像机得清点空间了
Better clear some space on my DVR.
新的《丑闻》要上映
There's a new Scandal.
你现在可以放心与我共进晚餐
Well, you can have dinner with me,
因为我要跟我老婆离婚了
because I'm leaving my wife.
你是怎么回事啊
Uh, hello? What happened?
他刚跟你说要跟老婆离婚
Dude told you he was gonna leave his wife,
你就逃得比误进男同酒吧的普京还快
and you left faster than Vladimir Putin at a gay bar.
俄罗斯总统普京去年七月立法禁止"非传统两性关系"
并可应用到同志或支持同志的外国旅客
我惊讶到记忆直接断片了
It's all a blur. I blacked out.
我都记不得我是怎么来这里的了
I don't even know how I got here.
应该是坐火车吧  麦克斯
I think I took the train, but, Max,
但也可能是堕落到坐了公车
I might have taken the bus.
他这消息太突然了
It came out of nowhere.
我从没想过他会跟老婆离婚
I never expected him to leave his wife.
这消息的源头
It came out of your thumbs
就是你发给他短信的贱拇指
when you texted it to him.
我跟他发那条短信时
Look, when I texted him that,
就只是在挑逗他嘛
I was just being flirty.
姐不穿胸罩去时代广场的
Flirty is me not wearing underwear
巧克力豆店才叫挑逗好吗
to the Times Square M&M store.
所以你真不想他跟老婆离婚吗
So you really don't want him to leave his wife?
当然不想
No!
我的确是有这么意淫过
I mean, sure, maybe I fantasized about it,
但幻想中我们是在雪乡滑雪
but in my fantasy we were on a ski trip,
然后我很兴奋地跟我最好的朋友
and I was jumping up and down, excited,
珍妮佛·劳伦斯一起上蹦下跳
with my best friend Jennifer Lawrence.
美国年轻女演员  出演过《饥饿游戏》系列
《美国骗局》等  已得过奥斯卡最佳女主与女配奖
你下次被垃圾桶边的负鼠吓到时
Cool, maybe call Jen next time
记得打电话让你好友阿珍来救你啊
the possum traps you by the garbage cans.
我以为我跟他就只是在消磨时间  图一乐嘛
Look, I thought we were just having a fun distraction.
也就是随便亲几下  偶尔"磨蹭磨蹭"
You know, a couple kisses, a dry hump here and there.
那种只乱不淫  成绩高分的"校花"吗
Oh, like the cheerleaders with the good grades.
美国学校里的拉拉队成员通常都是校园美女
但她们普遍成绩较差  私生活颇为淫乱
没错  我不是那种
Exactly. I'm not the type of person
会破坏别人婚姻的人
who wants him to leave his wife.
对  你是那种
No, you're the type of person
差一点就要破坏别人婚姻的人
who almost wants him to leave his wife.
没错没错  我就是这样
Yes! Yes, that's me!
我就是传说中的"差一点"女孩
I'm the "almost" girl.
我曾25次差一点失去我的童贞
I almost lost my virginity 25 times.
我高中时每周一跟我朋友的
This was my conversation with my friends
对话就是这样
every Monday in high school:
"那个了吗"
"Did you?"
"差一点"
"Almost."
有意思  因为我差一点就去念高中了
Funny, 'cause I almost went to high school.
麦克斯  我得想办法阻止尼可拉斯
Max, I have to figure out what to do about Nicolas
以防他差一点就铸成大错
before he almost makes a big mistake
离开他的老婆
and leaves his wife.
他才不会为了你而离开他老婆
He's not leaving his wife for you.
男人对美女说这种话
It's just a thing you say
只是为了骗她们上床
to pretty women to get them into bed.
就好像"我是俄罗斯的王子"
Like, "I'm a Russian prince,"
或是"你的故事真有意思"
Or, "That was a good story."
你有这么多款式的紧身小背心
With a tank top collection like yours,
哪还用得着编瞎话骗女人上床啊
I'm surprised you have to say anything.
就是说嘛
I know, right?
所以你觉得他不是真的要离开他老婆吗
So you don't really think he's serious about leaving her?
不是  我跟大把女人说过
No. I've told dozens of women
我会为了她们离婚
I'm leaving my wife for them,
而我根本没有结婚
and I'm not even married.
至少在美国没有
Here in America.
奥列格太好了
That was nice of Oleg.
当你觉得你对一个人已经有全面的了解时
Just when you think you've seen every part of a person--
因为他把"每一面"都用手机发给你看了
'cause he's shown you on his phone--
他却给你惊喜
He surprises you.
我现在感觉好多了
Oh, I feel so much better.
尼可拉斯不会离开他老婆
Nicolas is not going to leave her.
当然不会  他怎么会为了你离开他
No, why would he leave her for you?
你也不用说这么难听的话吧
Well, you don't have to be nasty about it.
麦克斯  尼可拉斯又发短信跟我说
Max, I just got another text from Nicolas
他要离开他老婆
about him leaving his wife.
奥列格  现在又说他明天四点
Oleg, now he says he's telling his wife
就要跟他的老婆摊牌
tomorrow at 4:00 that he's leaving her.
还有时间表啦
You got a timeframe?
如果他有订下时间表  那就是真的了
Oh, if he puts a clock on it, it's happening.
上菜了  甜瓜
Pick-up, cantaloupe.
麦克斯  他连摊牌时间都定好了
Max, there's a clock on it.
他老婆不是在法国吗
But isn't his wife in France?
是啊  但他们每天都视频聊天
Yeah, but they Skype every day.
他们就像法国版的《杰森一家》
They're like the French Jetsons.
《摩登原始人》的科技太空版本
他要用视频来说分手吗
He's gonna Skype break up with her?
这招太贱了
That is low.
也很聪明  或许某天我会偷来用
And smart. Might steal that move one day.
太好了  我看你手腕好很多了嘛
Oh, good, I see your wrist is better,
过来帮帮我吧
and I'm gonna need some help.
大扫除变得有一点点小棘手
The cleaning situation has gotten a little complicated.
两个蜘蛛团伙正在大战呢
The spider communities are at war.
阿憨  我没空打扫
Han, I can't clean.
我正忙着处理破坏别人婚姻的事呢
I'm in the middle of ruining someone's marriage.
那拜托你了  麦克斯  战事正急速加剧
Then, Max, please. Things are escalating quickly.
因为有一块掉在地上的火腿
There was a discarded piece of ham,
现在两国都认为那是它们的
and apparently both kingdoms thought it was theirs.
没人要去吗
Oh, no takers?
好吧  看来发短信没什么用
All right, enough with all this texting.
我得阻止这件事
I need to stop this.
我明天就去他家
I have to go over to his place tomorrow
面对面跟他说清楚
and tell him face to face.
面对面跟他说
Tell him face to face?
姐连做爱都不面对面做好吗
I don't even have sex face to face.
但愿尼可拉斯能接受我斩断情丝这件事
I hope Nicolas takes my breaking it off with him okay,
因为在我与他分手的幻想中
Because in my fantasy when I told him,
他不愿意接受我跟他分手
he wouldn't take no for an answer,
还给我买了架飞机
bought me a plane,
我就用飞机送了詹妮弗·劳伦斯回家
and I gave Jennifer Lawrence a ride home.
在我的幻想中
In my fantasy,
一条会说话的龙给了我一条
a talking dragon gave me a cape
属于耶稣的披风
that belonged to Jesus.
不过可能是因为我早些时候
But that's probably because I took too many
吃了太多迪克的维柯丁
of Deke's vicodin earlier.
楼下管理员说了你要上来
The lobby told me you were on your way up.
卡洛琳  我真没料到你会来
Caroline, I did not expect you.
所以你料的是我来吗
But you knew I'd be coming?
我们需要谈一谈  麦克斯是来给我打气的
We need to talk, and Max is here for moral support.
我已经知道她的作用了
I know how this works by now.
进来吧
Come in.
好吧  我该怎么说呢
Okay, how do I put this?
我该怎么说呢
How do I put this?
尼可拉斯  我今天来是要告诉你
Nicolas, I came here today to tell you...
不要这样做
To not do that.
为什么  我超级想要你
But why? I want you so much.
不是的  你才不想要我
Okay, you-- you don't want me.
你根本不了解我
You don't even really know me.
我了解你
I do.
你性感风趣  漂亮聪明
You're sexy and funny and pretty and smart.
好吧  你是有那么点了解我
Okay, you know me a little.
我不是那种会破坏人家婚姻的女人
Look, I am not the type of person who breaks up marriages.
对  她是那种"差一点"女孩
No, she's the "almost" girl.
她只差一点破坏别人婚姻
She almost breaks up marriages.
对  没错  我就是那种人
Yes, yes, that's who I am.
所以我不想你打给你老婆
So I don't want you to make that call
然后通过视频聊天跟你老婆离婚
and break up with your wife over Skype.
我不会在视频聊天时跟她提离婚
I am not breaking up with her over Skype.
好  非常好  那就不视频
Okay, great, perfect. No Skype.
不视频
No.
因为现在在大堂按铃的就是她
Because that's her in the lobby.
我要当面跟她说离婚
I'm breaking up with her in person.
我的老天  按铃那个是你老婆吗
Oh, my God, that's your wife in the lobby?
你老婆来了吗
Your wife is here?
我们应该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
冷静  我能搞定
Calm down. I can fix this.
给我一撮假胡子  一把辣椒粉
You need a fake mustache, a fistful of paprika,
和一本新护照
and a new passport.
如果这三样东西不全
If you don't have all three of those things,
只有两样也行
I can make it work with two,
但假胡子一定要有
as long as one of them is a mustache.
这里没有其他出口
There's no other way out.
快点  麦克斯  我们得马上离开这
Come on, Max, we have to get out of here now.
对了  还有
Oh, oh, yeah, and, uh,
不要因为我而跟你老婆离婚
don't leave your wife for me.
我们到此为止
Whatever we had, it's over.
还有
Oh, and...
这事不应该拖累我在学校的表现
this shouldn't reflect badly on me in school,
老娘废了半天劲才得到那个C-呢
'cause I worked hard for that c-minus.
先别走  站住站住
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
好吧  不过是因为她刚出了电梯
Okay, but only because she just got out of the elevator.
不能被她发现我在这里  我不能成为这种女人
She can't find me here. I can't be this girl.
我不能成为破坏他们婚姻的婊子
I don't want to be the whore he's leaving her for.
那是我最喜欢苏斯博士的一本书
That's my favorite Dr. Seuss book.
美国二十世纪最卓越的儿童文学作家之一
卡洛琳  你这话是什么意思
Caroline, what are you saying?
难道一直以来你都在误导我吗
You were just leading me on this whole time?
别这么说  法国臭鼬
Hold it, Pepe Le Pew.
没错  我一直等考完试才敢这么叫你
And, yes, I've been saving that one for after finals.
不能全赖卡洛琳
It is not just Caroline.
你追她比滚动甜甜圈大赛中
You're been chasing after her harder than a fat kid
追着甜甜圈的小胖仔还紧
in a Rolling Doughnut contest.
-没错  -等等  卡洛琳
- That's true. - Wait, wait, Caroline.
我和你到底还有没有可能
Do we still have a shot or not?
没可能
No.
那你最好赶紧躲进浴室
Then better go hide in the bathroom.
我可不想为此而婚姻破裂
I don't want this screwing up my marriage.
什么
What?
如果你不打算跟我在一起
Well, if you're not going to be with me,
那我干嘛要离开我老婆
I'm going to have to stay with my wife.
我可是个血气方刚的男人  离不开女人
I mean, I'm a man. I cannot be alone.
赶紧躲起来
Now, go, go, go.
不能被她发现你在我公寓里
She cannot find you here in our apartment.
你干嘛不直接告诉她
Why don't you just tell her the truth,
咱俩之间是清白的
that nothing happened between us?
她不会相信的
She will not believe me.
因为我有前科
I have a history.
可这里有两个人呢
There are two of us here.
我也有那种前科
I also have that history.
尼可拉斯  是我
Nicolas, c'est moi.
拜托你赶紧走
Now go, please.
你都要毁掉我人生了  赶紧行行好吧
That's the least you can do after ruining my life.
是差一点  差一点就毁掉你的人生
Almost. Almost ruined your life.
快走  麦克斯
Come on, Max.
这场面真是太让我为难了
This is totally inconvenient.
你最好把我的分数从C提到B
My "C" better go up to a "B."
太没下限了  我们居然像两个廉价妓女
This is crazy, us hiding in a married man's bathroom
躲在已婚男人的浴室里
like a couple of cheap floozies.
到目前为止  我听见的只是
So far, I'm just hearing a factual depiction
你对事实的陈述
of what's happening here.
我去看看什么情况
Let me see what's going on.
完全听不懂
I can't understand them.
我以为你懂法语呢
I thought you spoke French.
只能在美国人面前显摆
Only enough to impress Americans.
我要去厕所[法语]
Je dois utiliser les toilettes.
天啊  厕所
Oh, my god. Les toilettes.
她说的就是这里
Les toilettes, that's where we are.
她要进来了  我们该怎么办
She's coming in here! What should we do?
假装我们是性感的水管工吗
Pretend we're hot plumbers?
快躲进淋浴间里
Hide in the shower.
我觉得她会看见我们呢
I think she might notice us.
你们知道这全是玻璃吧
You know that's all glass, right?
我给你拿个干净的擦手毛巾
Let me just get you a clean hand towel.
她要尿尿
She has to pee-pee.
她不能进来用马桶
She can't come in here to use the toilet,
因为我屎一般的人生先占了
'cause my life is in it.
我知道  这真是太不幸了
I know, this is unfortunate.
那你们从窗户走吧
So go out the window.
你说什么
What?
没问题的
It's not a problem.
外面有个足够宽的窗沿  你们可以从那
There's a ledge wide enough for you to walk
走到邻居家的阳台  然后跳过去逃走
to the neighbor's terrace, jump, and get away.
斯蒂芬妮就这么做
Stephanie did it.
斯蒂芬妮是谁
Who's Stephanie?
那不重要
That's...not important.
重要的是她人没事
She's fine.
快走  你们必须得离开
Now go. You have to go.
除非你觉得我们之间还有可能
Unless you think you and I still have a shot.
我现在就上窗沿
I'll be on the ledge.
快点  麦克斯
Come on, Max.
不要  不可能  露西
No way, not happening, Lucy.
如果他失去这段烂婚姻
If he loses his bad marriage,
那我就是凶手
I'm responsible.
差一点  差一点就是凶手
Almost. Almost responsible.
麦克斯  如果不是为了把你弄进烘培学校
Max, I wouldn't even be in this situation
我就不用跟他一起工作
if I wasn't working with him to
更不会沦落在今天这个田地
put you through pastry school.
所以怪我咯
Oh, so this is my fault?
麦克斯  你就当是你的错吧
Max, please just let it be your fault.
完全是可行的
It's completely doable.
对了  外面在下雨呢
By the way, it's raining.
走吧  我们可以的
Come on. We can do this.
我们在家楼顶爬上15英尺高
We've crawled 15 feet on our roof
就为了偷电视信号
to get illegal cable.
那是为了看《绝命毒师》的最终集
Yeah, for the Breaking Bad finale!
就算摔死也在所不惜
Something worth dying for!
天啊  你疯了吗
Oh, my God, are you insane?
快进来
Get back in here!
麦克斯  或许你是对的
Max, maybe you're right.
我们应该用性感水管工的那招
We should've taken the hot plumber route.
我现在就回去
I'm coming back.
我的腿吓得走不动了
My legs won't go!
麦克斯  拉我回去
Max, help me back!
妈的  我恨死你了  贱人
Damn it. Damn it, bitch.
她进厕所了
She's in the bathroom.
她把窗户关上了
Oh, she closed the window.
而且还锁上了  现在没回头路了
and she locked it. So go.
往前走吧
Go, go!
如果斯蒂芬妮能做到  我们也能
If Stephanie did it, we can too.
真不敢相信因为他  我们得"铤而走险"
I can't believe we're up here all because of him.
我看人真是没眼光
I am such a bad judge of character.
废话  看你选我当你最好的朋友就知道
Of course you are. I'm your best friend.
麦克斯  对不起  这真是太惨了
Max, I'm sorry. This is bad.
至少不会更惨了  除非我们摔下去
Well, at least it can't get any worse, unless we fall.
或者开始下冰雹
Oh! Or it starts to hail!
哎哟  砸"雹"老娘了
Ow! Ow! Hurts like "hail!"
他们走了  快走
It's clear! Come on!
-我不想死  -我也是
- I don't wanna die! - Me neither!
真是奇了怪了
That's weird.
我人生中第一次不想死
For the first time in my life, I don't want to die.
我有了男朋友和我人生第一个"B"
I have a boyfriend and my first "B."
妈的  老娘内心变柔软了
Oh, God, I'm getting soft!
我不能死  我还没东山再起呢
I can't die! I haven't made my comeback yet.
我还幻想着  咱俩会搬进我从詹妮弗·劳伦斯
In my fantasy, you and I move into that penthouse
那里买来的的顶层公寓
I bought from Jennifer Lawrence.
还有屋顶花园哦  就在那边  看见了吗
Right over there, with the roof garden, see?
你们俩没事吧
Are you two all right?
虽然我不认识你俩
I mean, whoever you are.
我死了吗
Am I dead?
差一点  差一点就死了
Almost. Almost dead.
我的老天爷
Oh, my God.
你们俩怎么搞的
What happened to you two?
我们撞破了一扇窗
Well, we crashed through a window.
超屌的
It was pretty dope.
有点像电影《虎胆龙威》
It was kinda like a Die Hard movie,
如果他们在电影里也让女人耍酷的话
if they ever let girls do cool stuff in those movies.
脖子还好吗
The necks all right?
我们颈部扭伤了  我背部也受伤了
We have whiplash, and I have some bruises on my back.
麦克斯摔得最重  不过她不觉得疼
Max took the brunt of the fall but feels nothing
因为她体内主要成分是维柯丁
because she's mostly made of vicodin.
很高兴你没事
Well, I'm glad you survived,
因为如果你不在我身边
because I don't know what I would do
我不知道该如何是好
without you around here.
这话真窝心  厄尔
Aw, thanks, Earl.
其实我指的是你
I meant you.
我知道
I know.
麦克斯  你怎么会这么有劲
Max, how were you ever strong enough
用一只手就把我拉回来
to hold me up with one arm?
我小时候就经常用那只手
It's the arm I used to drag my mother
把我妈从酒吧里拽出来
out of bars with as a baby.
我有话要对你说
Well, I want to say something to you.
我想让你知道  如果在窗沿
I hope you know that if you were the one
滑倒的那个人是你
that slipped on that ledge--
我肯定就死了吧
I would be dead.
很高兴你能明白这个道理
Well, I'm glad that's out in the open.
各位安安
Hey, everybody!
我有近况要通报
I have an update about my life!
你们俩怎么搞的
What happened to you two?
苏菲  我们发生了意外  说来话长啊
Sophie, we had an accident. It's a long story.
你的故事都很长
Yeah, all of yours are.
我要退出电影圈
Well, I'm out of the movie business.
我跟电影公司的的那位大假发分手了
I broke up with my bigwig from Miramax.
我们大吵了一架
We got in a huge fight,
他还拿他的大假发扔我
And he threw his big wig at me.
他警告我永远别想在这城市里吃上午饭
He told me I'd never eat lunch in this town again.
而我说
And I said,
"如果我在市里
"Hey, if I'm in town,
姐饿了就会去午饭  宝贝"
I'm eating lunch, baby!"
不是吧  甭装了
Oh, no. No, no, no,
我全身到处被蜘蛛咬得遍体鳞伤
I don't have spider bites over half my body
不是为了让你们俩能继续装病的
so you two could fake another injury.
想得美
Nice try.
一定很疼吧
Ooh, I'll bet that hurts.
目 前 资 金
最 新 余 额